Congratulations you've finished the lessons on motion planning,
and with the tools you've developed,
you're ready to complete your next project.
In this project, you'll again be flying in a simulator,
but this time in a more complicated 3D environment.
So Andy, how is this going to work?
Well Nick, basically, we're going to take
the methods and the algorithms that you've laid out in these lessons,
and going to combine them to build an amazing 3D motion planner.
So, Nick's laid out a lot of material in the past several lessons.
And now, it's up to you to design and build
a motion planner for your quadcopter. But don't worry.
I'm going to show you how to build up
that baseline implementation that you need for this project.
And then, if you're feeling inspired,
you can take it to the next level with some of
the more advanced techniques that Nick presented.
How does that sound to you Nick?
That sounds pretty good to me Andy.
I can't wait to see what you build.